travelperk.com 2017-05-28

# Privacy Policy | TravelPerk

* ### GENERAL INFORMATION

The use of the webpage www.travelperk.com (the “ **Website** ”) offered by TRAVELPERK, S.L.U a company duly incorporated under the laws of Spain, with its domicile at Via Augusta 21-26, 6ª, 08006 Barcelona (Spain), provided with Spanish Tax Identification Number (CIF) nº B-66-484.577 and registered with Barcelona Mercantile Registry, Volume 44779, Page 131, sheet B-467263 (“TravelPerk”), implies necessarily to gather some information about its clients and their employees who will be the users of the Website.

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Website (“ **Users** ”).

In this Privacy Policy you will find accurate description about (i) the data collected about TravelPerk’s clients and their employees, (ii) the purpose of gathering such information, and (iii) how the use of such information can be managed and controlled by TravelPerk.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to all the services offered on the Website, as well as pages and services that may be added to the Website in the future, and is subject to the terms and conditions provided by Law 15/1999, from December 13, on Personal Data Protection (“ **LOPD** ”), the Royal Decree 1720/2007, from December 21, which develops LOPD (“ **RLOPD** ”), and Law 34/2002, from July 11, on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce (“ **LSSI** ”).

* ### TYPE OF DATA COLLECTED BY TRAVELPERK

In order to provide the services offered, TravelPerk will collect, among others, corporate information of the Users, such as the name, surname, e-mail address, password, phone number, payment data, and other professional and personal data from the clients and its employees.

The Users guarantee the authenticity and veracity of all data provided through the Website and shall update any information provided to TravelPerk, so that it always corresponds to the real and current situation. The Users shall be responsible for any false or inaccurate statements made and any damages it may cause to TravelPerk or any third parties.

Likewise, TravelPerk may also collect other User’s data, such as information on how Users use the Website, using cookies; and log file information, including the IP address, browser type, URLs, number of clicks, and how you interact with links, domain names, landing pages and pages viewed.

TravelPerk will manage the collected data pursuant to the applicable law and according to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy. In any case, TravelPerk does not collect information about health, race, ideology, religion, beliefs, trade union membership or sex life.

* ### IDENTITY OF THE RESPONSIBLE OF PROCESSING DATA

The personal data collected will be incorporated into a data file under TravelPerk responsibility.

* ### USE OF PERSONAL DATA

The personal data provided to TravelPerk will be used to process and manage the services you have requested from TravelPerk at all times. TravelPerk may also use personal data to:

  * Manage and control the Users’ transactions and provide the services purchased by them through the Website.
  * Manage and control the Users’ compliance with the terms and conditions of our Website and their accounts;
  * Manage and control your user account in the Website;
  * Send advertising or promotional communications, by electronic means, of the services and products offered by TRAVELPERK, S.L.U, in accordance with Article 21 of Spanish Law 34/2002, of 11 July, of Services Information Society and Electronic Commerce.

TravelPerk guarantees that personal information will not be shared to any third parties for their use unless prior consent given to do so or unless TravelPerk is obligated by law.

TravelPerk may retain certain information associated with the Users account in its files for analytical purposes. The periods for which information will be retained depends on the purpose for which this information is collected.

TravelPerk will not retain personal information for longer than necessary for its business purposes or as required by the law. TravelPerk may retain some information for a period of time after closing the user account with TravelPerk, for instance if this is necessary to meet any legal obligations.

Personal data processed will not be put to uses incompatible with the purposes for which such data were collected. Data processing for historical, statistical or scientific aims shall not be deemed to be incompatible uses.

TravelPerk will not use the personal data for different purposes other than those mentioned above, unless prior notification to the Users granting a reasonable term so the Users can oppose to it.

* ### SECURITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY MEASURES APPLIED TO DATA

TravelPerk has implemented and maintains appropriate, administrative, technical, and organizational measures according to the type of data collected, and subject to the terms and conditions set forth in the RLOPD, to protect the personal information provided to TravelPerk against unauthorized or unlawful access, and against accidental loss, damage, alteration or destruction of the data. Only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions. Notwithstanding the above, there may be wrongful acts committed by third parties even if TravelPerk uses all means at his disposal to avoid such acts.

Despite the foregoing, it is the Users’ responsibility to properly safeguard keys and passwords supplied for their access, and prevent unauthorized use or access by third parties. TravelPerk shall not responsible for the misuse of the username and password carried out by any user.

* ### MANAGING PERSONAL DATA (ARCO RIGHTS)

In any case, users can exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition (in particular, not to receive advertising or promotional communications) (“ **ARCO Rights** ”) regarding their data by writing a communication to the following address: TRAVELPERK, S.L.U, Via Augusta 21-26, 6ª, 08006 Barcelona, Spain; or to the following email: personaldata@travelperk.com.

* ### SENDING PROMOTIONAL OFFERS

By accepting this Privacy Policy Users consent TravelPerk to use the e-mail addresses provided by them to send promotional offers by e-mail or by any other equivalent means of electronic communication, in accordance with Article 21 of Spanish Law 34/2002, of 11 July, on Services Information Society and Electronic Commerce.

Where applicable, the Users will be asked if they wish to receive promotional offers related to goods and services marketed or offered by TravelPerk’s partners or collaborating entities, or by any other third party, provided that such information is referred to similar or related services to the ones provided by TravelPerk.

* ### REVISION OF PRIVACY POLICY

TravelPerk may review this Privacy Policy at any time. The current Privacy Policy will be available at all times in the Website. All updates will be effective immediately upon its publication.

* ### ACCEPTANCE

By providing their personal data to TravelPerk and signing up as users and/or using the Website, Users expressly accept the use of their personal data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to, the commercial communications and storage of their data.

* ### GOVERNING LAW AND COMPETENT JURISDICTION

The Website and this Privacy Policy are governed by Spanish law. Any dispute arising from this Privacy Policy or any claim related to the content and services of the Website shall be resolved by the courts of Barcelona (Spain). Effective Date: 16th May 2017
